Guide to the Kenneth S. Pitzer, President of Stanford University, Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, circa 1968-1970
  - Education and World Affairs-Invitations
    - Federal Aid/Partner to Education, 1966-1968 (Box 4B)
    - Fonacier, Mrs. Tomas S., 1963-1968 (Box 4B)
    - Form letters - introductions abroad, jury duty, queries from retiring military etc. (Box 4B)
    - Founding Grant (Box 4B)
    - Fraternities, 1962-1968 (Box 4B)
    - Free Student (Box 4B)
    - Free University of Berlin, 1954-1967 (Box 4B)
    - Freshmen convocation, 1964-1967 (Box 4B)
    - Graduate Coordinating Committee (Box 4B)
    - Guest Rooms (Box 4B)
    - Hanna House (Box 4B)
    - Haskins Laboratoies (Box 4B)
    - Hazing - fraternities and eating clubs (Box 4B)
    - Hebrew University (Box 4B)
    - Institute of Intercollegiate Studies (Box 4B)
    - Institute of Metropolitan Studies (Box 4B)
    - Institute of The Study of the Future, 1968 (Box 4B)
    - Institute of Urban Studies, 1968 (Box 4B)
    - Institiutional Services, Inc., 1968 (Box 4B)
    - Insurance - general, 1955-1968 (Box 4B)
    - Insurance - Medical Plans (Inc. Major Medical), 1955-1966 (Box 4B)
    - Inter-Racial Happenings, 1967 (Box 4B)
    - INTERACT - group designed to help Negroes at Stanford and East Palo Alto (Box 4B)
    - Intercollegiate Society of Individualists, 1967 (Box 4B)
    - International Living, 1966 (Box 4B)
    - Invitations to speak (accepted), 1969-1970 (Box 4B)
    - Invitations from student groups, 1968-1970 (Box 4B)
    - Invitations to speak (regretted), 1969-1970 (Box 4B)
    - Invitations to speak (undecided), 1967-1970 (Box 4B)
    - Invitations, 1969-1970 (Box 4B)
    - Invitations - inaugurals, convocations, dedications, etc., 1969-1970 (Box 4B)
  - Judicial Procedures-University of California
    - Judicial Procedures, 1963-1969 (Box 5B)
    - Lawrence Radiation Laboratories (Box 5B)
    - Liquor Policy, 1962-1967 (Box 5B)
    - Madmoiselle Magazine, 1967 (Box 5B)
    - Mid-Peninsula Free University, 1966-1968 (Box 5B)
    - Mid-Peninsula Observer, 1968-1969 (Box 5B)
    - National Commission on Accrediting, 1959-1964 (Box 5B)
    - National Geographic Society, 1968 (Box 5B)
    - Bill of Rights - National Student Association, 1965 (Box 5B)
    - Pacific Eight - recruiting (code, ethics, etc.), 1959-1962 (Box 5B)
    - Council meeting minutes and agenda Pacific Eight Conference, 1969-1970 (Box 5B)
    - Pacific Eight meeting, 1968 Sep 3-4 (Box 5B)
    - Pacific Eight conference - minutes, agendas, 1968-1969 (Box 5B)
    - Palo Alto - Stanford Liaison Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 5B)
    - Parks Job Corps, 1965 (Box 5B)
    - Peace Corps, 1965-1968 (Box 5B)
    - People To People, 1963-1968 (Box 5B)
    - Peterson, Mr. T. S. (Ted) Trustee, 1961-1964 (Box 5B)
    - Pi Lamba Theta (Honorary and Professional Association for Women), 1965 (Box 5B)
    - Philanthropic Digest, 1967 (Box 5B)
    - Pake Committee (an organization of private universities), 1967 (Box 5B)
    - Palo Alto Chamber of Commerce (Box 5B)
    - Policy - campus residences, 1953-1963 (Box 5B)
    - Clinical and Other Staff Privileges Policy (includes golf, athletic, bookstore, etc.), 1960-1965 (Box 5B)
    - Policy - demonstrations, 1963-1969 (Box 5B)
    - Policy - discipline, 1964-1967 (Box 5B)
    - Poor's Register of Corporations, directors and executives (Box 5B)
    - Prince Charles (Box 5B)
    - Probe (Auxilliary Jacket) other material checked out to Mr. Glover (Box 5B)
    - The Public Interest (Box 5B)
    - Questions/Questionnaires, 1969-1970 (Box 5B)
    - Stanford Campus Recreation Associates (Box 5B)
    - Refusals, 1965-1970 Aug (Box 5B)
    - Research for World Peace (Box 5B)
    - Lord Earl Bertrand Russell, the philosopher (Box 5B)
    - Russian Embassy, 1965 (Box 5B)
    - Santa Clara County Inter - City Council (Box 5B)
    - Santa Clara County Supplementary Education Center (Box 5B)
    - Satire Group, 1967 (Box 5B)
    - School of Freedom, 1966-1967 (Box 5B)
    - Senior Brunch (Box 5B)
    - Senior Colloquia (Dr. Sterling), 1964-1969 (Box 5B)
    - Senior Fund Reception, 1968 (Box 5B)
    - Seniors - general (Box 5B)
    - Sigma Delta Chi, 1965 (Box 5B)
    - Southern education report, 1965 (Box 5B)
    - Speakers, 1968-1969 (Box 5B)
    - Stanford Association of University Scholars (Box 5B)
    - Stanford Christian Council (Box 5B)
    - Stanford-Santa Clara Ecumenical Colloquium (Box 5B)
    - Stanford Shopping Center, 1966-1970 (Box 5B)
    - Stanford Student Congress (Box 5B)
    - Stanford Survey Research Center, 1965 (Box 5B)
    - Petition for Signal at Willow R. Pastear, 1968 (Box 5B)
    - Stone, Robert E., 1967 (Box 5B)
    - Student Conference On Nataional Affairs (SCONA) (Box 5B)
    - Student Congress (Box 5B)
    - Student Faculty Board (Box 5B)
    - Student Initiative Fund at Stanford (Box 5B)
    - Student Project in Community Health Resources for the Poor, 1966 (Box 5B)
    - Sylvania Property Story (a subsidiary of GTand E Lab, Inc.), 1963-1966 (Box 5B)
  - Resignations
    - Regisnations (handling of notes of thanks) (Box 6B)
    - Research contracts - authorization to accept and execute contracts (Box 6B)
    - Students - general, 1956-1958 (Box 6B)
    - Students Voluntary Organizations (Box 6B)
    - Summer School of World Affairs, 1963-1967 (Box 6B)
    - Tahoe Paradise College (Box 6B)
    - Task Force on Education, 1968 (Box 6B)
    - Tax on Gifts To Higher Education (includes Pomona Planlife income gifts), 1955-1961 (Box 6B)
    - Tax deductions for graduate students, 1966 (Box 6B)
    - Policy for faculty of other tenure universities (Box 6B)
    - Tobacco, 1963-1968 (Box 6B)
    - Trends, 1967 (Box 6B)
    - Trustees - Fraternity House Evaluation Committee, 1963 (Box 6B)
    - University of California, 1967-1969 (Box 6B)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1965-1969 (Box 6B)
    - U.S. Department of State - International Education Exchange Service - NATO Service Program (Box 6B)
    - U.S. Department of State - International Scientific and Technological Affairs, 1965-1966 (Box 6B)
    - Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs United States Senate Committee, 1966 (Box 6B)
    - USMPC (United Student Movement Peace Club), 1966 (Box 6B)
    - Valentine, David R., 1960-1963 (Box 6B)
    - Vision, 1965 (Box 6B)
    - Visitors, 1968-1969 (Box 6B)
    - Weekly, The Stanford, 1966 (Box 6B)
    - Western Personnel Institute, 1955-1963 (Box 6B)
    - Western Politics (Box 6B)
    - White House Conference on Education, 1966 (Box 6B)
    - Whiteford. William K., 1960-1968 (Box 6B)
    - Workshop, The (Undergraudate Bi-Weekly), 1966 (Box 6B)
    - World of Learning Publication - annual report, 1961-1965 (Box 6B)
    - World Student Conference, 1962-1965 (Box 6B)
    - Young, Frank E. (San Diego), 1959-1963 (Box 6B)
    - Young Presidents Organization, 1965-1966 (Box 6B)
    - The Youth Participation in Community Action Project, 1966 (Box 6B)
    - University of California Extension Program, 1953-1963 (Box 6B)
    - University Club of Palo Alto, 1963-1965 (Box 6B)
    - University of the Pacific - includes proposal of State Financial Medical Education, 1965 (Box 6B)
    - Visiting Committees - general correspondence, 1962-1968 (Box 6B)
    - Visitors, 1969-1970 (Box 6B)
    - Visitors - foreign, 1968-1969 (Box 6B)
    - Visitors - foreign, 1969-1970 (Box 6B)
    - French visit, 1970 Feb 19 (Box 6B)
    - Pompidou visit, 1970 Feb 27 (Box 6B)
    - Western Association of Schools and Colleges/Western College Association, 1963-1969 (Box 6B)
  - Committees
    - Committee Reogranization, Committee on, 1958-1964 (Box 7B)
    - Academic Council - corespondence, 1964-1969 (Box 7B)
    - Academic Senate - general correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 7B)
      - Re: membership and privileges of the Senate (Box 7B)
      - Question of allowing press coverage of Senate/Council meetings (Box 7B)
      - Senate rules (Box 7B)
    - Academic Council - Memorial Resolutions, 1960-1968 (Box 7B)
    - Academic Council, Executive Committee - Minutes of the, 1967-1968 (Box 7B)
    - Advisory Board, 1968-1969 (Box 7B)
      - Working Papers re: Reconstitution of the Advisory Board (Box 7B)
    - Admissions (Undergraduate) - minutes and reports (Box 7B)
      - Non-academic staff to serve on committees (Box 7B)
      - Suggestions for non-academic staff to serve on committees (Box 7B)
      - Controversy over the selection of students for Packer Committee (Box 7B)
      - Students on Committees (Box 7B)
    - University Advisory Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 7B)
    - Committee on Alumni Conferences, 1967-1968 (Box 7B)
    - Committee on Athletics and Physical Education, 1969-1970 (Box 7B)
      - Committee meeting minutes - Committee on Athletics and Physical Education (Box 7B)
    - Committee on Awards, Prizes and Honors (Box 7B)
    - Faculty Consultative Group on Campus Disruptions, 1968-1969 (Box 7B)
    - Comission on Dissent - to examine violence at Stanford (Box 7B)
    - Committee on Low-Cost Housing, 1968-1970 (Box 7B)
    - Financial Aid - student, 1966-1969 (Box 7B)
    - Committee on Financial Awards, 1968-1969 (Box 7B)
    - Foreign Visitors and Students, Committee on (Box 7B)
    - Committee on General Studies, 1966-1969 (Box 7B)
    - Graduate Studies Division, 1967-1969 (Box 7B)
    - Committee on Health Insurance/Medical Coverage (Box 7B)
    - Residence Problems Committee (short term), 1969 (Box 7B)
    - Committee on International Studies, 1967-1968 (Box 7B)
    - Visiting Committee International Studies, 1967-1969 (Box 7B)
    - International Studies Subcommitteee on African Studies, 1967-1968 (Box 7B)
    - Committee on the Undergraduate Program In African and Afro-American Studies, 1968 (Box 7B)
    - East Asian Studies, 1966-1967 (Box 7B)
    - International Studies Subcommitteee on Latin American Studies, 1967-1968 (Box 7B)
    - International Studies Subcommitteee on Libraries, 1966 (Box 7B)
    - International Studies Subcommitteee on Western European Studies, 1966-1967 (Box 7B)
    - Advisory Committee on Land and Building Development, 1969-1970 (Box 7B)
      - Membership and Role of Committee on Land and Building Development, 1966-1969 (Box 7B)
    - Subcommitteee on Faculty Housing (minutes and other), 1967-1970 (Box 7B)
    - Long Range Education Goals and Planning (Box 7B)
    - Minority Employment, 1968 (Box 7B)
      - Minority Employment Representatives (Box 7B)
    - Human Relations Committee (Box 7B)
      - Tresider store incident, 1968 (Box 7B)
    - Interim Judicial Body (Faculty Appeals Board) (Box 7B)
    - Temporary Judicial Council, 1968 (Box 7B)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Memberships and Privileges to the Senate, 1969 (Box 7B)
  - Committees and Other
    - Educational Inquiry Committee - Quarter vs Semester, 1955-1966 (Box 8B)
    - Provost Committee - Committee on Improvement of Library Coordination and Cooperation, 1969 (Box 8B)
    - Library Council, 1969 (Box 8B)
    - Minority Programs Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 8B)
    - University Operations Review Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 8B)
    - Committee on Overseas Campuses, 1968 (Box 8B)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Parking Regulations, 1968-1969 (Box 8B)
    - Subcommitteee on Standards Committee on Public Exercises (Box 8B)
    - Public Exercise Committee - Commencement, 1968 (Box 8B)
    - Public Exercises - Lectures and Film Subcommitteee, 1968 (Box 8B)
    - Concert and Special Events Subcommitteee, 1968 (Box 8B)
    - Subcommitteee on Policy Public Exercise Committee, 1968 (Box 8B)
    - Public Exercises - Subcommitteee on Public Ceremonies, 1968 (Box 8B)
    - Public Exercises, 1966-1969 (Box 8B)
    - Public Exercises - Subcommittee on Gowns (Box 8B)
    - Public Health, Committee on, 1967-1968 (Box 8B)
    - Radio, T.V. and Motion Pictures, Committee on, 1967 (Box 8B)
    - Radiological Hazards Control Committee established, 1963-1965 (Box 8B)
    - Academic Council Committee on Research Policy, 1966-1969 (Box 8B)
    - Committee on Residential Policies Subcommittee (Steering Committee), 1967 (Box 8B)
    - Committee on ROTC (Reserve Officer Training Corps) - President's Advisory, 1969 (Box 8B)
    - ROTC (Reserve Officer Training Corps) Scholarship Selection Board, 1968 (Box 8B)
    - Salary Committee (Presidents's Advisory), 1969 (Box 8B)
    - Security Committee, 1968 (Box 8B)
    - Committee on Standards (auxiliary jacket due to loss of original in fire), 1966-1967 (Box 8B)
    - SLAC (Stanford Linear Accelerator Center Program) Coordinating Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 8B)
    - SRI (Stanford Research Institute) Relationship Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 8B)
    - Editorial Advisory Committee of Stanford Today, 1966 (Box 8B)
    - Rushing - policies, procedures, etc., 1963-1965 (Box 8B)
    - Student Affairs and Services, Committee on (Box 8B)
    - Student Conduct Legislative Council, 1968 (Box 8B)
      - Re: Recommended Changes in Legislative and Judicial Council of, 1968 (Box 8B)
      - Re: Appointmens of the Committee (Box 8B)
      - SLAC (Stanford Linear Accelerator Center Program) Proposed Resolution Allowing Certain Schools Within the University to Establish their own Judicial Bodies (Box 8B)
    - Student-Faculty Employment Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 8B)
    - Ad Hoc Senate Committee on Relations with Student Government, 1968-1969 (Box 8B)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Student Involvement in Political Process Through, 1970 (Box 8B)
    - Succeed-Committee Developed From the Educatonal Opportunites for Disadvantaged Minorities, 1965-1966 (Box 8B)
    - Administrative Committee For Summer Quarter Programs, 1966 (Box 8B)
    - Teacher Education, Committee on, 1969 (Box 8B)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education Studies, 1966-1969 (Box 8B)
    - University Publications, Committee on, 1969 (Box 8B)
    - Committee Review the University's Visiting Committee's Structure and Organization, 1969 (Box 8B)
  - Speeches by Dr. Pitzer
    - Gift summaries/general information (Box 9B)
    - Mothers Club of Stanford University (Box 9B)
    - Man and Technology - commencement address at Harvey Mudd College, 1961 Jun 5 (Box 9B)
    - Education for Tomorrow's World National Teacher Education Conference, 1958 Jun 24 (Box 9B)
    - Atomic Engergy Commission - before the southern California section of the American Chemical Society, 1952 Mar 7 (Box 9B)
    - Gifts to Pitzer (Box 9B)
    - General correspondence A-Z (Box 9B)
    - San Francisco dinner honoring Dr. Pitzer, 1969 Apr 23 (Box 9B)
    - American Chemical Society (Box 9B)
    - Bohemian Club (Box 9B)
    - California Academy of Sciences (Box 9B)
    - Council and conference on higher education in the American Republics (Box 9B)
    - Dover/Prentice Hall Publications (Box 9B)
    - Honors and awards/invititations to same (Box 9B)
    - Memberships (Box 9B)
    - Menlo Country Club (Box 9B)
    - Pitzer - move to Stanford, 1968-1969 (Box 9B)
    - National Committee of the U.S. Peoples Fund for the United Nations, Inc. (Box 9B)
    - National Confernence of Christian and Jews (Box 9B)
    - Plaudits (Box 9B)
    - Rice University (Box 9B)
    - United Negro College Fund (Box 9B)
    - Holiday greetings, 1968 (Box 9B)
    - Priestley Award Address - American Chemical Society: effecting national priorities for science, 1969 Apr 14 (Box 9B)
    - SRI (Stanford Reserach Coalition) - remarks by Dr. Pitzer, 1969 Apr 9 (Box 9B)
    - Stanford East Bay Women's Club, 1969 Apr 9 (Box 9B)
    - Pitzer Remarks To Trustees re: Stanford Research Institute (SRI) - Stanford Relationship, 1969 Apr 8 (Box 9B)
    - Remarks To LASSU, 1969 Apr 3 (Box 9B)
    - President Pitzer (on The Report and Recommendations of the Stanford Judicial Council ), 1969 Feb (Box 9B)
    - The Atom and the Nation - Oakland Rotary Club, 1958 Mar 13 (Box 9B)
    - Opportunities and Responsibility - Commencement of Texas A and M, 1962 May 26 (Box 9B)
    - Excerpts from Inaugural Address at Rice, 1962 Oct 10 (Box 9B)
    - Scientist, Astronauts, and Politicians - 95th Charter Day Ceremonies, University of California, 1963 Mar 22 (Box 9B)
    - The Task Ahead Commencement, Bayloff School of Medicine, 1963 June 15 (Box 9B)
    - Role of the Universities and the Government in Science - Golden Jubilee convocation of Texas West College, 1964 May 21 (Box 9B)
    - Advanced Education and Modern Technology - Rotary Club, Pasadena, 1964 Oct 2 (Box 9B)
    - 10 year Plan 1965 - 75 - Associates Dinner, 1964 Dec 3 (Box 9B)
    - How Much Research - Houston Philosophical Society, 1965 Jan 21 (Box 9B)
    - Matriculation Address Rice University, 1965 Oct 3 (Box 9B)
    - Orthodoxy and Dissent - 2nd Commencement, Pitzer College, 1966 June 5 (Box 9B)
    - Expanding Role for Colleges at Rice University - Hanzen College, 1967 Feb 22 (Box 9B)
    - To the Board of Governors and Friends of Rice University, 1966-67 (Box 9B)
    - Quality Crisis in Higher Education - New York Chemists Club, 1968 Mar 19 (Box 9B)
    - University Integrity - Commencement At the University of St. Thomas, 1968 May 17 (Box 9B)
  - Departments
    - Admissions, General, 1969-1970 (Box 1C)
    - Admissions, Future, 1966-1967 (Box 1C)
    - Admissions, General, 1967-1969 (Box 1C)
    - Admissions, General, 1960-1970 (Box 1C)
    - Admissions, Minority Recruitment - includes Admissions Policy Change (minorities), 1968-1969 (Box 1C)
      - Pro and con letters (Box 1C)
    - Admissions, Transfers, 1968-1969 (Box 1C)
    - Admissions, Undergraduate - A-L, 1968-1969 (Box 1C)
    - Admissions, Undergraduate - M-Z, 1968-1969 (Box 1C)
    - Admissions - A-H, 1967 (Box 1C)
    - Admissions - I-Z, 1967 (Box 1C)
    - Admissions, Undergraduate Lists, 1967-1968 (Box 1C)
    - Admissions, Old Cases (Box 1C)
    - Admissions, Transfers, 1967-1968 (Box 1C)
    - Architecture (History of Attempts To Accelerate Architecture Program) (Box 1C)
      - includes Strengthening Program in Architecture - lectures from alumni, architects, etc., 1961-1965 (Box 1C)
    - Art Gallery and Museum, 1963-1969 (Box 1C)
    - Business Office (VP for Business Affairs), 1968-1970 (Box 1C)
    - Business, Graduate School of, 1968-1970 (Box 1C)
    - Business, School of, Sloan Program, 1961-1970 (Box 1C)
    - Computer Science Visiting Committee (Box 1C)
    - Advisory Council (Visiting Committee School of Engineering), 1966-1969 (Box 1C)
    - General Secretary's Office, 1967-1969 (Box 1C)
    - Graduate Division, 1968-1969 (Box 1C)
    - Finance, Director of, McFadden (Box 2C)
    - Finance, Vice-President For (Box 2C)
    - Law School Board of Visitors, 1968-1969 (Box 2C)
    - Medical School, 1968 (Box 2C)
    - Medical School Department-Honoring …, 1969 (Box 2C)
    - Medical School Fund Raising (Box 2C)
    - Medical School Articles of Organization By-Laws (Box 2C)
    - Visiting Committee Medical School (Box 2C)
    - Stanford in Britian, 1966-1969 (Box 2C)
    - Stanford Summer Institute on Germany (Box 2C)
    - Stanford Center For Japanese Studies in Tokyo, 1960-1964, 1966 (Box 2C)
    - Stanford In Taipei, Stanford Center for Chinese Studies, 1962-1964 (Box 2C)
    - Personnel, 1967-1971 (Box 2C)
      - Includes personnel-identification cards (Box 2C)
    - Physical Education Department, 1968-1969 (Box 2C)
      - Includes president's courtesy list, 1969-1970 (Box 2C)
    - Physical Education - Women (Box 2C)
      - Includes elimination of graduate programs (Box 2C)
    - Big Game Away (Box 2C)
    - Big Game (Football), 1968 (Box 2C)
    - Reunions - BigGame, 1965-1967 (Box 2C)
    - Rose Bowl Game, 1968 (Box 2C)
    - Rose Bowl Game, 1969 (Box 2C)
    - BYU (scheduling policy) (Box 2C)
    - Police Services to the Stanford Campus (Box 2C)
    - Police and Fire Department (Box 2C)
    - President Kenneth S. Pitzer includes Dr. Kenneth S. Pitzer, president of Stanford, 1968 Dec 1 (Box 2C)
      - Dr. Pitzer resigns as president (Box 2C)
    - Vice-President and Provost-Richard Lyman, 1966-1970 (Box 2C)
    - Staff duties and assignments while Dr. Lyman is acting president, 1970 (Box 2C)
    - Acting President, Richard W. Lyman, 1970 (Box 2C)
    - Psychology, Building dedication, 1970 (Box 2C)
    - Public Events (Box 2C)
    - Secretary of the University, 1961-1971 (Box 2C)
    - Speech Pathology and Audiology (Box 2C)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President For (Box 2C)
  - Gifts/classified research
    - Gifts - A (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - B (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - C (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - D (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - E (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - F (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - H (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - I (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - J (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - K (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - L (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - MA-MC (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - ME-MZ (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - N (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - O (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - P (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - R (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - S (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - Standard Oil Company gifts (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - T (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - U (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - V (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - W (Box 3C)
    - Gifts - XYZ (Box 3C)
    - University libraries non-monetary gifts (Box 3C)
    - Non-monetary - art gallery and museum, 1956-1964 Sep (Box 3C)
    - Gifts-non-monetary (miscellaneous), 1960-1968 (Box 3C)
    - Non-monetary gifts, 1954-1960 (Box 3C)
    - Non-monetary gifts-art gallery and museum, 1964 Sep (Box 3C)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 3C)
      - Machine records/controller, 1969-1970 (Box 3C)
    - Classified research closed (Box 3C)
      - Classfied research, 1952-1968 (Box 3C)
      - Phase-out/follow-up classified research-(correspondence with contract officers, etc.), 1967-1970 (Box 3C)
      - Working papers - classified research (Box 3C)
  - Budgetary papers (Box 4C)